<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://PatLittle.github.io/GC-Pod_Hub2/index.html</id>
    <title>GC-Pod-Hub</title>
    <updated>2025-02-12T07:28:42.791Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://PatLittle.github.io/GC-Pod_Hub2/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://PatLittle.github.io/GC-Pod_Hub2/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk #4: The Long Fight for Porters' Rights]]></title>
        <id>9bff9f9c-94ac-41bf-8be7-271eaa16ed0b</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/9b21ab00"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T13:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the inhumanity of portering, and the long fight for porters’ rights. (Episode 4) 
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk: Episode 4 Trailer]]></title>
        <id>37fe8654-e1c0-48ae-9ba8-17c324d48496</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/28ea30a3"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T13:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the inhumanity of portering, and the long fight for porters’ rights. (Episode 4 trailer)
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping Happiness: How Where We Live Impacts Our Well-Being]]></title>
        <id>164ed1f3-b00f-436f-b837-3ed4db957167</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/a1bbe7b5"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might not surprise you that your relationships with friends and family affect your well-being. Same with your health and your job. But what about the place where you live? Whether you live in the downtown core of a major city or a commuter town or a rural community, what impact does this have on your life satisfaction, loneliness and sense of belonging? StatCan’s Lauren Pinault joins us today at the mic to explore how the places we live affect our well-being. 
For more information:
Beyond urban and rural: Rethinking the social geography of Canada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calculating crop rotation for potatoes]]></title>
        <id>14f81efc-ce67-4e79-a1c6-24979d695f02</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f67f1c9"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T12:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lori Robinson, a 6th generation farmer in PEI, is a data hound.  As a result of her 50+ years of her and her family taking detailed notes and 20 + years of doing a four-year crop rotation system she laid the groundwork for a user-friendly calculator for crop rotations that has both economic benefits for producers and environmental benefits. Developed at the Living Labs initiative in PEI in conjunction with the PEI Potato Board, the calculator helps producers maximize profits while reducing their use of pesticides and improving soil health. And the story of the calculator has some interesting twists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consommation de substances, stigmatisation et dépendance chez les hommes travaillant dans des métiers spécialisés]]></title>
        <id>85c5b2a8-aff0-4c0b-a1dc-e8bd93aff446</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/consommation-de-substances-stigmatisation-et-dpendance-chez-les-hommes-travaillant-dans-des-mtiers-spcialiss"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La stigmatisation à l’égard de la consommation de substances influe sur la façon dont nous parlons aux personnes, sur les politiques que nous élaborons et sur la prestation des soins. Dans cet épisode, la Dre Theresa Tam, administratrice en chef de la santé publique du Canada, et Anne Tennier, présidente et première dirigeante du CCHST, discutent des façons de réduire la stigmatisation et de soutenir les hommes dans les métiers spécialisés qui font face à des difficultés.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Substance Use, Stigma and Addiction Among Men in Trades]]></title>
        <id>63504b4a-ba35-4fc9-a5f0-e0452d81e6ca</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/substance-use-stigma-and-addiction-among-men-in-trades"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stigma surrounding substance use affects how we talk to individuals, the policies we develop, and how we provide care. In this episode, Dr. Theresa Tam, Chief Public Health Officer of Canada, and Anne Tennier, President and CEO of CCOHS, discuss ways we can reduce stigma and support men in the trades who are struggling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk #3: All Aboard the Hotel on Wheels]]></title>
        <id>d3f3f1b3-3459-429f-bff7-1bcc8083ddaf</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/0f534256"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T17:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us as we explore the extraordinary demands placed on sleeping car porters by rail companies and passengers while working aboard the hotel on wheels. We will also hear about the various ways these men resisted and rose above anti-Black racism. (Episode 3)
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plant breeding: Long-game innovation in a fast-changing world]]></title>
        <id>0da13d28-3f6b-4792-9488-53041f71679b</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/c0465e78"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T12:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How has plant breeding evolved over the past 20 years? Who are the players in Canada? What is the plant breeding continuum? And what is the proverbial sandbox in which Canadian plant breeders are working? Learn this and why it takes a special breed of innovator to become a plant-breeder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Les principales questions sur la santé et la sécurité de 2024]]></title>
        <id>cb192858-134c-48f9-b756-1f3a27e944b2</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/les-principales-questions-sur-la-sant-et-la-scurit-de-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chaque année, le CCHST reçoit des questions sur la santé et la sécurité de tout le Canada. Nous discutons avec l’un de nos spécialistes techniques des questions les plus importantes et les plus fréquentes de l’année.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Health and Safety Questions of 2024]]></title>
        <id>74077b19-6d79-48b8-943e-d0e630f45b21</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/top-health-and-safety-questions-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the year end roundup you’ve been waiting for: the top health and safety questions you asked us in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk: Episode 3 Trailer]]></title>
        <id>abe16f7c-2658-4768-bbbc-094395749262</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/ce4a9565"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the dire working conditions porters experienced as they traversed the country aboard the hotel on wheels. (Episode 3 trailer)
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Your Business Outsmart a Hacker?]]></title>
        <id>60467fc2-787b-4bbd-8b5e-fc2386a9a485</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/fbacf553"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over two thirds (70%) of Canadians experienced a cyber security incident in 2022. The strategies used by bad actors are getting more and more complex. Many of us are inundated with what feels like never-ending phishing emails, scam text messages and fraudulent phone calls. It’s rare to talk to someone who hasn’t experienced some form of a cyber attack. 
The situation is no different for Canadian businesses. Identity theft, scams, fraud, and ransomware are only some of the ways cyber attackers are targeting businesses today. One cyber security breach can cost a business thousands of dollars and valuable time resources to neutralize. We wanted to know: Is cyber crime on the rise in Canada? What is the relatively new phenomenon of cyber risk insurance? And in what way are consumers affected when a business experiences a security breach? 
The Canadian Survey of Cyber Security and Cyber Crime has published new data and, in this episode, we sat down with Howard Bilodeau, an economist at Statistics Canada to answer our questions about how cyber security is changing for businesses and what it means for the rest of us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevent Slips, Trips and Falls with Good Workplace Housekeeping]]></title>
        <id>45ec7e15-47db-4839-9777-7d96fcd2b21d</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prevent-slips-trips-and-falls-with-good-workplace-housekeeping"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good workplace housekeeping might seem like a simple concept, but it doesn’t always get the respect it deserves. Learn how effective housekeeping can reduce the risk of slips, trips and falls, one of the most common lost-time injuries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prévenir les glissades, trébuchements et chutes grâce à une bonne tenue des locaux de travail]]></title>
        <id>812d8c5b-d57e-4ef3-bd1a-e7bd7fb65889</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prvenir-les-glissades-trbuchements-et-chutes-grce-une-bonne-tenue-des-locaux-de-travail"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La bonne tenue des locaux de travail peut sembler un concept simple, mais elle n’est pas toujours reconnue à sa juste valeur. Découvrez comment une tenue efficace des locaux peut réduire le risque de glissades, de trébuchements et de chutes, qui sont à l’origine de blessures entraînant une absence au travail parmi les plus courantes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk #2: Who Were the Porters?]]></title>
        <id>12A3A9C9-8BDB-4D3D-B945-5C2EA0BFF66E</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/52bae4d3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2) 
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI Coming For Your Job?]]></title>
        <id>2971075b-a807-4ed4-83ea-d3fb9e1f2c02</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/8b36bff9"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is here and it’s here to stay. Apps like ChatGPT are now allowing us to perform complex tasks with the click of a button.  
  
As we begin to use these new versions of AI, our jobs are destined to change. So, what will an average day of work look like a decade from now? Which jobs will AI impact the most? And is AI coming to replace our jobs altogether?   
  
In this episode, we sat down with AI expert Tahsin Mehdi, an economist in the social analysis and modeling division of Statistics Canada, to answer our questions about how AI will transform our work lives in Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk: Episode 2 Trailer]]></title>
        <id>03BDE169-9511-4C30-8A99-DAE71CF62BAA</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/958a8685"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2 trailer) 
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Workers from Bird Flu]]></title>
        <id>3873c66f-90fe-45f4-9669-5a9c32be2903</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protecting-workers-from-bird-flu"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Farms experiencing a surge in bird flu infections can put people who work with poultry and dairy cattle at risk of catching the illness. In this episode, we talk with CCOHS Senior Technical Specialist Matea Kokorovic about measures you can take to protect your workers.
  
Released: September 13, 2024
 File Size:  2.5 MB
 Length:  5:01 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protéger les travailleurs contre la grippe aviaire]]></title>
        <id>905f777f-49a4-4b9c-9c4e-6de8f496d432</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protger-les-travailleurs-contre-la-grippe-aviaire"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les exploitations qui connaissent une recrudescence des infections par la grippe aviaire exposent les personnes qui travaillent avec les volailles et les bovins laitiers au risque de contracter la maladie. Au cours du présent épisode, nous nous entretenons avec Matea Kokorovic, spécialiste technique principale du Centre canadien d’hygiène et de sécurité au travail au sujet des mesures que vous pouvez prendre pour protéger vos travailleurs.
  
Date de diffusion : 13 septembre 2024
 Taille du fichier : 3 MB
 Durée : 5 : 45 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk #1: Honouring Stanley G. Grizzle - An Activist For Our Times]]></title>
        <id>4E5D6216-6E83-4EC1-BF06-9604FEEF8EE0</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/483c1bfa"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T12:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the life of the man who recorded the stories of the porters working on the rails. (Episode 1) 
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk: Episode 1 Trailer]]></title>
        <id>93B266C9-63B3-4A7A-90BD-97D501EA7A05</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/69f33af4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T19:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the man who turned the microphone over to the porters to record their experiences working on the rails. (Episode 1 trailer)
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porter Talk: Trailer]]></title>
        <id>07A30928-2DE6-4B23-9536-1672E250557A</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/fb5f3d58"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T17:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Their voices, along with those of their wives and children, relay stories of both hardship and resilience. (Podcast series trailer)
Transcript
Narrator Biographies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Discover Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work]]></title>
        <id>1e4088fe-13f9-4d45-b52e-1ec7b0e0fa5b</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/sparking-courageous-conversations-at-work"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T18:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holding courageous conversations in the workplace can help to advance equity, diversity, and inclusion. Learn how to start these discussions, and how they can foster greater understanding, connection, growth, and even healing.
  
 Released:  August 8, 2024
  File Size:   3 MB
  Length:  5:28 minutes
  
 -------------------------
 « Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work »     
 Tenir des conversations courageuses sur le lieu de travail peut contribuer à faire avancer l’équité, la diversité et l’inclusion. Apprenez comment entamer ces discussions et comment elles peuvent favoriser une meilleure compréhension, une meilleure connexion, une meilleure croissance et même une meilleure guérison.
  
Date de diffusion : 8 août 2024
 Taille du fichier : 3 MB
 Durée : 5 : 28 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Economists Are Sounding the Alarm on Productivity]]></title>
        <id>8da518c5-bc3d-42b3-85e5-96a4db1a0ee6</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/7b2071ff"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada’s workforce is among the most educated in the world. But when it comes to worker productivity, we’ve seen a real slump over the past few years. The quarterly data published by StatCan in June 2024 confirms Canadian workers are continuing to underperform compared to our neighbours to the south. This comes as no surprise to this episode’s guest, Guy Gellatly, Chief Economic Advisor at StatCan. The latest quarterly numbers are a continuation of an on-going decline in Canada’s productivity that economists have been tracking for years.  
 
But what factors influence worker productivity? And why does it matter if Canadians are less productive? As a matter of fact, what even is productivity? In this episode, we asked Guy to help us understand how we got to this point and why it matters for Canadians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science vs. food waste]]></title>
        <id>dd21b812-2416-472a-83b6-9eb7b1b8b68a</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f8e0c6e"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can we make biodegradable plastics using food waste? Can we control disease in crops and eliminate food borne pathogens using just hydrogen peroxide, ozone and UV rays? Yes, we can! Meet the two grand prize winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge – in the novel technology stream -- who proved we can do this and more. 
Learn how Genecis Bioindustries and Clean Works are fighting food waste and food loss with cutting-edge science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the intersection between IP law and the protection of Indigenous knowledge and cultural expressions.]]></title>
        <id>ba3301d5-9a98-4b25-af67-1fb88a170000</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/exploring-the-intersection-between-ip-law-and-the-protection-of-indigenous-knowledge-and-cultural-expressions-6_dwPtEd"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vincent de Grandpré, lawyer and trademark agent at Bennett Jones and member of IPIC’s Committee for Indigenous IP explains the intersection between intellectual property law and the protection of Indigenous knowledge and cultural expressions. 
 
Explore online: 

Indigenous peoples and intellectual property (canada.ca)
Indigenous Bar Association
Implementing the United Nations Declaration on the Rights of Indigenous People Act (justice.gc.ca)
Indigenous Traditional Knowledge (ipic.ca)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s an urban forest?]]></title>
        <id>tag:soundcloud,2010:tracks/1836700347</id>
        <link href="https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/whats-an-urban-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re going to explore the world of urban forests and hear about how they can transform concrete jungles into vibrant livable spaces. We reached out to a couple of experts from the Canadian Forest Service to talk about the ins and outs of urban forest management. This episode is also a double feature, with our friends from the Statistics Canada podcast “Eh-sayers” talking about the ironies of data when it comes to the environment. Both stories share a common theme: “it’s not easy being green.”

Recommended Links:
•	What trees should I plant in an urban forest? (Simply Science Video) – https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=paRluAdUiAw 
•	More Trees to Plant in an Urban Forest (Simply Science Video) – https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bhq3O15LKZw 
•	Download the My Tree app! (NRCan App) – https://natural-resources.canada.ca/our-natural-resources/forests/sustainable-forest-management/my-tree/19974]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simply Science</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Not Easy Bein' Green]]></title>
        <id>feb8cba4-2f09-4c5d-bd27-ca681f454662</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/54f7dce8"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can try our best, but its not always easy knowing what's best for the environment. The world is complicated, and it isn't as simple as reduce, reuse, recycle—though that's a great place to start!
In the immortal words of Kermit the Frog, "It's not easy bein' green."
We have two stories exploring that theme. The first is one we made in-house asking just how green our digital world really is, and the second comes from the Simply Science podcast exploring the world of urban forests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety]]></title>
        <id>829b9dea-62b5-45e2-8ef3-c098f3815af8</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/how-plain-language-improves-workplace-health-and-safety"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When employers commit to using plain language, they make it easier for workers to do their jobs. They also help to support a more inclusive workplace. In this episode, we talk with plain language expert Jocelyn Pletz about how clear and simple communication can improve health and safety.
  
Released: June 5, 2024
 File Size:  8.2 MB
 Length:  14:26 minutes
  
-------------------------
 « How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety »   
 Lorsque les employeurs s’engagent à utiliser un langage clair, ils facilitent le travail des travailleurs. Ils favorisent aussi l’inclusivité dans le milieu de travail. Dans cet épisode, nous parlerons avec Jocelyn Pletz, spécialiste du langage clair, qui expliquera comment les communications claires et simples peuvent améliorer la santé et la sécurité.
  
Date de diffusion : 5 juin 2024
 Taille du fichier : 8.2 MB
 Durée : 14 : 26 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing Neurodiversity in the Workplace]]></title>
        <id>2126d26b-0fc7-4011-9fd7-ff90480d8322</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/embracing-neurodiversity-in-the-workplace"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we chat with Dr. Marie-Hélène Pelletier, a psychologist and business leader, about embracing neurodiverse conditions such as attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, dyslexia, and autism spectrum disorder, in the workplace.
  
  Released:  May 13, 2024
  File Size:   6.9 MB 
 Length:  14:17 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faire place à la neurodiversité au travail]]></title>
        <id>7727cd67-f13f-45ce-9c71-f75f03c134a1</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/faire-place-la-neurodiversit-au-travail"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T19:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dans cet épisode, nous discutons avec Marie-Hélène Pelletier, Ph. D., psychologue et chef des opérations, au sujet d’adaptation à la neurodiversité, comme le trouble d’hyperactivité avec déficit de l’attention, la dyslexie et le trouble du spectre de l’autisme en milieu de travail
  
Date de diffusion : 13 may 2024
  Taille du fichier :  8 MB
  Durée :  17 : 04 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Food Inflation Is Such a Hard Nut to Crack]]></title>
        <id>8a226c65-58a1-4f64-947f-48a7196f57e8</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/97b2d26e"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you feeling like it's a little bit harder to bring home the bacon... from the grocery store? The latest data indicate that food prices have mostly stabilized... but why does it feel like the cost of feeding your family is still going up?
Today we're talking food inflation with StatCan's resident smart cookie Taylor Mitchell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the IP agent profession is regulated]]></title>
        <id>5f4813ba-7749-4ec4-be87-eea99783dc79</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-the-ip-agent-profession-is-regulated-2LEqe6Zv"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juda Strawczynski, CEO and Registrar of the College of Patent Agents and Trademark Agents (CPATA) explains how CPATA regulates the IP agent profession, ensuring that patent agents and trademark agents deliver accessible, ethical and expert IP services in Canada.
Explore online:

CPATA Public Register
CPATA Code of Professional Conduct]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (CPATA, College of Patent Agents &amp; Trademark Agents, Canadian Intellectual Property Office, CIPO)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenge accepted!]]></title>
        <id>de8ab330-1ddf-409d-b855-81eb1f61222b</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/0a6bab0c"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T12:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the two winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge (Business Models Stream)
Two companies took away $1.5 M! Find out who they are. Learn what it took to become the winners of the challenge, and leaders in this new sub-sector. The funds will help the winning companies further expand their success in fighting food waste and reducing greenhouse gases.  And, we’ll give you a glimpse behind the scenes with Dr Jean-Charles Le Vallée, who will share insights into being a jury member of the challenge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 16]]></title>
        <id>4438BE47-2608-412E-8122-BED1F29D7178</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/81acd6cf"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hammering of the last spike into the Canadian Pacific Railway expanded access to the nation immeasurably, physically and symbolically connecting it from coast to coast. While seen as a victory in the dominant narrative of Canada, it served as a catalyst for the mass displacement of Indigenous peoples and the exploitation and even death of labourers involved in the construction of the railway. Join us as Marcelle Cinq-Mars delves into the historic image depicting this moment, and we reflect on the real human cost that was paid in the name of progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's 8 pm...Do You Know What Your Kids Are Googling?]]></title>
        <id>e393f7c8-ebde-499c-81de-9db6f93698a5</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/8710dcf9"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T04:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StatCan released new analysis into the online culture our kids are growing up in, and it’s far from the best of all possible worlds: misinformation, bullying, violence… and worse.
Analyst Rachel Tsitomeneas joins us to dive into the findings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story]]></title>
        <id>ee047a8c-ad50-4224-add2-41d616f6ff55</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/day-of-mourning-melanie-kowalski-flemings-story"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T14:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Mark was not one to go to the hospital. If he could duct tape or crazy glue it to fix it, he would. This was so much more than what duct tape or crazy glue could fix.” Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s life changed forever the day her husband fell off a ladder at work. Hear her powerful story.
  
Released: April 8, 2024
 File Size:  7.5 MB
 Length:  13:20 minutes
  
 -------------------------
 « Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story »
 « Mark n’était pas du genre à aller à l’hôpital. S’il pouvait régler le problème avec du ruban adhésif ou de la colle, il le faisait. Mais cette fois, le ruban adhésif et la colle n’y pouvaient rien. » La vie de Melanie Kowalski-Fleming a changé pour toujours le jour où son mari est tombé d’une échelle au travail. Écoutez son histoire percutante.
  
Date de diffusion : 8 avril 2024
 Taille du fichier : 7.5 MB
 Durée : 13 : 20 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What innovators need to know about the Competition Bureau]]></title>
        <id>dd1733fd-2bbd-4289-add8-2d628f00c946</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/what-innovators-need-to-know-about-the-competition-bureau-Tjj37JmI"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Gunderson, senior economist and coordinator at the Economic Analysis Directorate at the Competition Bureau explains the Bureau’s mandate and actions when it comes to intellectual property.
Explore online:

Intellectual Property Enforcement Guidelines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Canadian Bureau of Competition, Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax time: What older Canadians and caregivers need to know]]></title>
        <id>4af4593c-4d63-40f6-9951-5b73d90b3905</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/tax-time-what-older-canadians-and-caregivers-need-to-know-u7OhrWN9"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the importance of filing your taxes on time, what tax credits are available for older Canadians and caregivers for the 2023 filing season, tips to help with filing, important dates and the CRA’s toll-free number, 1-800-959-8281.
Recommended links:  

What you need to know for the 2023 tax-filing season - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/newsroom/tax-tips/tax-tips-2024/what-you-need-to-know-2024-tax-filing-season.html
Get ready to do your taxes - https://www.canada.ca/en/services/taxes/income-tax/personal-income-tax/get-ready-taxes.html
Seniors: Simplify tax-filing so you can get back to doing what you enjoy! - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/newsroom/tax-tips/tax-tips-2024/seniors-simplify-tax-filing.html
Free tax clinics - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/services/tax/individuals/community-volunteer-income-tax-program.html
Seniors in Canada Facebook page - https://www.facebook.com/SeniorsinCanada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax time: What older Canadians and caregivers need to know]]></title>
        <id>4af4593c-4d63-40f6-9951-5b73d90b3905</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/tax-time-what-older-canadians-and-caregivers-need-to-know-u7OhrWN9"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the importance of filing your taxes on time, what tax credits are available for older Canadians and caregivers for the 2023 filing season, tips to help with filing, important dates and the CRA’s toll-free number, 1-800-959-8281.
Recommended links:  

What you need to know for the 2023 tax-filing season - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/newsroom/tax-tips/tax-tips-2024/what-you-need-to-know-2024-tax-filing-season.html
Get ready to do your taxes - https://www.canada.ca/en/services/taxes/income-tax/personal-income-tax/get-ready-taxes.html
Seniors: Simplify tax-filing so you can get back to doing what you enjoy! - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/newsroom/tax-tips/tax-tips-2024/seniors-simplify-tax-filing.html
Free tax clinics - https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/services/tax/individuals/community-volunteer-income-tax-program.html
Seniors in Canada Facebook page - https://www.facebook.com/SeniorsinCanada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Période des impôts : Ce que les aînés canadiens et les proches aidants doivent savoir]]></title>
        <id>f0739e97-c4a4-4727-b968-1bfe2ef17e0e</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/periode-des-impots-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-et-les-proches-aidants-doivent-savoir-SbfA8SpQ"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Découvrez l’importance de produire votre déclaration de revenus dans les temps et quels crédits d’impôt sont offerts aux aînés canadiens et aux proches aidants pour la période des impôts 2023. Obtenez également des conseils pour vous aider à produire votre déclaration et apprenez quelles sont les dates importantes. Voici le numéro sans frais de l’ARC : 1-800-959-7383.
 Recommended links:  
Ce que vous devez savoir pour la période des impôts de 2023 – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/nouvelles/salle-presse/conseils-fiscaux/conseils-fiscaux-2024/vous-devez-savoir-pour-periode-impots-2024.html
Préparez-vous à faire vos impôts – https://www.canada.ca/fr/services/impots/impot-sur-le-revenu/impot-sur-le-revenu-des-particuliers/preparez-vous-impots.html
Aînés : Simplifiez la production de votre déclaration de revenus pour rapidement retourner à vos passe-temps! – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/nouvelles/salle-presse/conseils-fiscaux/conseils-fiscaux-2024/aines-simplifiez-production-votre-declaration-revenus.html
Comptoirs d’impôts gratuits – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/services/impot/particuliers/programme-communautaire-benevoles-matiere-impot.html
Page Facebook des Aînés au Canada - https://www.facebook.com/AinesauCanada/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Période des impôts : Ce que les aînés canadiens et les proches aidants doivent savoir]]></title>
        <id>f0739e97-c4a4-4727-b968-1bfe2ef17e0e</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/periode-des-impots-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-et-les-proches-aidants-doivent-savoir-SbfA8SpQ"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Découvrez l’importance de produire votre déclaration de revenus dans les temps et quels crédits d’impôt sont offerts aux aînés canadiens et aux proches aidants pour la période des impôts 2023. Obtenez également des conseils pour vous aider à produire votre déclaration et apprenez quelles sont les dates importantes. Voici le numéro sans frais de l’ARC : 1-800-959-7383.
 Recommended links:  
Ce que vous devez savoir pour la période des impôts de 2023 – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/nouvelles/salle-presse/conseils-fiscaux/conseils-fiscaux-2024/vous-devez-savoir-pour-periode-impots-2024.html
Préparez-vous à faire vos impôts – https://www.canada.ca/fr/services/impots/impot-sur-le-revenu/impot-sur-le-revenu-des-particuliers/preparez-vous-impots.html
Aînés : Simplifiez la production de votre déclaration de revenus pour rapidement retourner à vos passe-temps! – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/nouvelles/salle-presse/conseils-fiscaux/conseils-fiscaux-2024/aines-simplifiez-production-votre-declaration-revenus.html
Comptoirs d’impôts gratuits – https://www.canada.ca/fr/agence-revenu/services/impot/particuliers/programme-communautaire-benevoles-matiere-impot.html
Page Facebook des Aînés au Canada - https://www.facebook.com/AinesauCanada/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combattre la fraude en la reconnaissant : Ce que les aînés canadiens doivent savoir]]></title>
        <id>a1c7ab15-8a84-4112-9056-163da7d487d7</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/combattre-la-fraude-en-la-reconnaissant-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-doivent-savoir-45XxdLpc"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T14:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury et Jeffrey Horncastle parlent du Centre antifraude du Canada, des principales fraudes envers les aînés canadiens, des mesures à prendre si vous êtes victime de fraude et de l’importance de signaler une fraude au Centre antifraude du Canada, soit en ligne ou en appelant le numéro sans frais 1-888-495-8501.

Centre antifraude du Canada : 

Francais - https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-fra.htm
Anglais - https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-eng.htm

Mois de la prévention de la fraude :

Français - https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/bureau-concurrence-canada/fr/fraude-arnaques/mois-prevention-fraude
Anglais - https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/competition-bureau-canada/en/fraud-and-scams/fraud-prevention-month

Guide de sécurité à l’intention des aînés, GRC :

Français - https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/fr/guide-securite-a-lintention-des-aines
Anglais - https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/en/seniors-guidebook-safety-and-security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combattre la fraude en la reconnaissant : Ce que les aînés canadiens doivent savoir]]></title>
        <id>a1c7ab15-8a84-4112-9056-163da7d487d7</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/combattre-la-fraude-en-la-reconnaissant-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-doivent-savoir-45XxdLpc"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T14:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury et Jeffrey Horncastle parlent du Centre antifraude du Canada, des principales fraudes envers les aînés canadiens, des mesures à prendre si vous êtes victime de fraude et de l’importance de signaler une fraude au Centre antifraude du Canada, soit en ligne ou en appelant le numéro sans frais 1-888-495-8501.

Centre antifraude du Canada : 

Francais - https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-fra.htm
Anglais - https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-eng.htm

Mois de la prévention de la fraude :

Français - https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/bureau-concurrence-canada/fr/fraude-arnaques/mois-prevention-fraude
Anglais - https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/competition-bureau-canada/en/fraud-and-scams/fraud-prevention-month

Guide de sécurité à l’intention des aînés, GRC :

Français - https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/fr/guide-securite-a-lintention-des-aines
Anglais - https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/en/seniors-guidebook-safety-and-security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting fraud with knowledge: What older Canadians need to know]]></title>
        <id>c9281058-24b6-4c7a-a1de-6d8e01e6df5a</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/fighting-fraud-with-knowledge-what-older-canadians-need-to-know-74Z9Ffwc"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T14:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury and Jeffrey Horncastle discuss the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC), tops scams targeting older Canadians, what to do if you have been a victim of fraud and the importance of reporting fraud to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre online or by calling the toll-free number at 1-888-495-8501.
Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre: 

English: https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-eng.htm
French: https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-fra.htm

Fraud Prevention Month:

English: https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/competition-bureau-canada/en/fraud-and-scams/fraud-prevention-month
French: https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/bureau-concurrence-canada/fr/fraude-arnaques/mois-prevention-fraude

RCMP Seniors Guide to Safety and Security:

English: https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/en/seniors-guidebook-safety-and-security
French: https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/fr/guide-securite-a-lintention-des-aines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting fraud with knowledge: What older Canadians need to know]]></title>
        <id>c9281058-24b6-4c7a-a1de-6d8e01e6df5a</id>
        <link href="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/fighting-fraud-with-knowledge-what-older-canadians-need-to-know-74Z9Ffwc"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T14:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury and Jeffrey Horncastle discuss the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC), tops scams targeting older Canadians, what to do if you have been a victim of fraud and the importance of reporting fraud to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre online or by calling the toll-free number at 1-888-495-8501.
Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre: 

English: https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-eng.htm
French: https://antifraudcentre-centreantifraude.ca/index-fra.htm

Fraud Prevention Month:

English: https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/competition-bureau-canada/en/fraud-and-scams/fraud-prevention-month
French: https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/bureau-concurrence-canada/fr/fraude-arnaques/mois-prevention-fraude

RCMP Seniors Guide to Safety and Security:

English: https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/en/seniors-guidebook-safety-and-security
French: https://www.rcmp-grc.gc.ca/fr/guide-securite-a-lintention-des-aines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jamie.nordstrand@hrsdc-rhdcc.gc.ca (Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Say "Language Revitalization" in Cree?]]></title>
        <id>6224fbe2-425e-4996-80e4-73ff569174c4</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/bd75c457"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 70 distinct Indigenous languages are spoken by First Nations people, Métis and Inuit in Canada, but these languages are under threat. 
In this episode, we speak with Randy Morin and Belinda kakiyosēw Daniels, who share their knowledge of the Cree language with learners at the Nêhiyawak Language Experience, about the wisdom encoded in Indigenous languages, as well as the opportunities for these languages and the barriers they face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comprendre les effets de la sensibilité aux parfums]]></title>
        <id>d4943ebe-03b2-411a-92f1-fea79dbd2705</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/comprendre-les-effets-de-la-sensibilit-aux-parfums"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pour certains travailleurs, l’eau de Cologne et les crèmes à mains peuvent sentir bon, mais pour leurs collègues qui présentent une sensibilité aux parfums, elles peuvent avoir des effets désagréables pour la santé. En fait, les réactions aux parfums, comme les maux de tête, les démangeaisons oculaires et les difficultés respiratoires, sont un problème de santé, et elles sont considérées comme une déficience au sens de la Loi canadienne sur les droits de la personne. 
  
  Date de diffusion : 18 mars 2024
   Taille du fichier : 3.3 MB
   Durée : 6 : 46 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense of Scent Sensitivities]]></title>
        <id>11264d74-31f6-46a0-8482-4f1e0b644104</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/making-sense-of-scent-sensitivities"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the scent of cologne or hand lotion may be pleasant to some, for co-workers with sensitivities to fragrances, they may have unpleasant health effects. In fact, reactions to scents, such as headaches, itchy eyes, and difficulty breathing, are a medical condition and recognized disability under the Canada Human Rights Act.  
  
 Released: March 18, 202
  File Size:  2.7 MB
  Length:  5:10 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that a robot in your field?]]></title>
        <id>2296d29d-d08d-4a10-be03-c187a46a8d36</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/a5bf9d8e"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ag-robotics specialists Chuck Baresich believes you’ll have a robot in your field sooner than you think.  What will they do? How will they add value to your farm? Chuck paints a picture of that future. And what is the government doing to help the agricultural sector be ready for those robots? Marco Valicenti, Director General of Innovation Programs Directorate and Brett Maxwell, Director of Strategic Policy Branch explain how Agriculture and Agri-Food Canada’s programs are enabling that future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is natural hydrogen the solution?]]></title>
        <id>tag:soundcloud,2010:tracks/1769171136</id>
        <link href="https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/is-natural-hydrogen-the-solution"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There seems to be a lot of excitement about natural hydrogen lately. But why is the level of interest peaking now? Could it be part of the solution to the climate crisis? Is it the environmentally friendly game changer everyone is looking for? Or not? To answer those questions and more, we reached out to one of our hydrogen experts, as well as a scientist from the University of Toronto.

Recommended Links:
•	Cleaner Digging with Hydrogen  - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/simply-science/cleaner-digging-hydrogen/21757 
•	The Hydrogen Strategy - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/climate-change/canadas-green-future/the-hydrogen-strategy/23080]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simply Science</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does IP fit into the world of scientific research and experimental development?]]></title>
        <id>a5f3cf7c-bc9e-490d-896f-54b5b55faffb</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-does-ip-fit-into-the-world-of-scientific-research-and-experimental-development-KJ3yT3ka"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Arsenault, Atlantic Regional Manager for the Canada Revenue Agency's Scientific Research and Experimental Development (SR&ED) Tax Incentive Program, demystifies the parallel worlds of R&D and IP from an SR&ED tax incentive program perspective.
Explore online:

SR&ED tax incentives
Self-Assessment and Learning Tool
SR&ED outreach program
Request a free telephone consultation with an SR&ED specialist
Income Tax Folio S3-F4-C1, General Discussion of Capital Cost Allowance
Consultation Paper: Scientific Research and Experimental Development
Consultation Paper: Creating a Patent Box Regime

Learn more about SR&ED eligibility guidelines:

T4088 SR&ED Guide to Form T661]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Canada Revenue Agency, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hiring smart]]></title>
        <id>837ed100-6407-49a9-a2b8-8a6b57de8e79</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/3fa7c93f"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hear from two innovators who are successfully tackling labor shortages in our sector: one at the national level with an all-encompassing, all-stakeholders-engaged strategy; and the other on a regional level with a smart program for hiring and settling new immigrants into a rural community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is I.P. managed when the government funds you to innovate?]]></title>
        <id>884fbfbc-c860-480b-97ed-6f5e7649ad17</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-is-ip-managed-when-the-government-funds-you-to-innovate-aRVGrLgS"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grant Lynds, a senior advisor on IP matters from the IP Centre of Expertise, sheds light on the role of this group and how IP considerations are addressed in government funding agreements.
Explore online:

Canadian Intellectual Property Office
Intellectual Property Centre of Expertise
College of Patent Agents and Trademark Agents
Intellectual Property Institute of Canada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Innovation Science and Economic Development, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musculoskeletal Disorders and Mental Health]]></title>
        <id>643d1f8f-820f-4c21-b34e-803e764abf83</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/musculoskeletal-disorders-and-mental-health"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Heather O’Reilly (nee Johnston) from McMaster University discusses the connection between musculoskeletal disorders and psychological factors, and what workplaces and workers can do to limit risks for injuries. 
  
Released: February 1, 2024
 File Size:  10 MB
 Length:  17:40 minutes
  
 -------------------------
 « Musculoskeletal Disorders and Mental Health »
 Heather O’Reilly (née Johnston), Ph. D., de l’Université McMaster explique le lien entre les troubles musculosquelettiques et les facteurs psychosociaux, et ce que les milieux de travail peuvent faire pour limiter les risques de blessures. 
  
Date de diffusion : 1 fevrier 2024
 Taille du fichier : 10 MB
 Durée : 17 : 46 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Straight talk about pesticides]]></title>
        <id>163107ec-f0e8-416e-b701-d7fa9d9e97f6</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/18d0d36f"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T14:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How is pesticide use evolving on farms? What are maximum residue limits? How does the government determine what is safe? Brian Rideout, a fruit and vegetable grower from Ontario, explains how pesticide use has changed on his farm in the last 20 years. And Fred Bissonnette, Executive Director of the Pest Management Regulatory Agency, explains the regulations behind pesticide use in Canada. Let's dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Feet Prevention: Steps to Stay Safe and Warm When Working Outdoors]]></title>
        <id>76225617-3fa6-4839-9dd1-6cada4ce0e7a</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/cold-feet-prevention-steps-to-stay-safe-and-warm-when-working-outdoors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With all the walking, standing, and working workers do on their feet, they can be exposed to potential injury. In winter, cold weather afflictions like frostbite, chilblains, and trench foot can cause painful and sometimes serious consequences.   
 
 Tune in to this CCOHS podcast to earn more about the harm that working in cold weather can cause feet, and how to put protections in place.
  
 Released:  January 9, 2024
 File Size:   3.7 MB
 Length:  6:58 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pour ne plus avoir froid aux pieds : comment rester au chaud et en sécurité lorsqu’on travaille dehors]]></title>
        <id>ac0b68c8-8953-4d8a-8777-ce825f991199</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/pour-ne-plus-avoir-froid-aux-pieds-comment-rester-au-chaud-et-en-scurit-lorsquon-travaille-dehors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T15:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[À tellement marcher, être debout et travailler sur leurs deux pieds, les travailleurs les exposent à des blessures potentielles. En hiver, les maux liés au temps froid comme les gelures, les engelures et le pied de tranchée peuvent avoir des conséquences douloureuses et parfois graves. 
  
 Ne manquez pas ce balado du CCHST pour en apprendre davantage sur les lésions aux pieds qui peuvent résulter du travail extérieur par temps froid et la façon de mettre en place des mesures de protection.   
  
Date de diffusion : 9 janvier 2024
  Taille du fichier :  4.6 MB
  Durée :  8 : 58 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use IP for financing]]></title>
        <id>972a05df-1932-45da-a075-b268d417ee61</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-to-use-ip-for-financing-nb8uhvQ3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kiriakoula Hatzikiriakos, Manager-Senior Legal Counsel in the Commercial/International sector of Legal Affairs at the National Bank of Canada, explains the rules and challenges of using IP as a collateral for funding.
Explore online:

BLOG | koulah
Intellectual Property-Backed Financing | BDC.ca]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Kiriakoula Hatzikiriakos, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Out in the Pod There Arose Such a Clatter, We Turned Our Mics On to See What Was the Matter]]></title>
        <id>367a8789-e9b1-4f01-9845-413e050a251d</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/a5c176b3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Twas the night before Christmas, when all through the studio
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse;
The stockings were hung by the audio mixer with care,
In hopes that a special guest soon would be there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 15]]></title>
        <id>189C07E9-1C25-4BAD-9400-5A7BBE02C918</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/a0cd2d05"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Treasures Revealed we follow the journey of a rare document which is considered to be the first publication in English entirely about Canada, with the help of Senior Special Collections Librarian Meaghan Scanlon. Once carelessly discarded, this broadside is later discovered in an unrelated publication, miraculously preserved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Less Misinformation, a Little More True Facts, Please]]></title>
        <id>1bae7bc4-99d7-440c-85d1-682edc844d52</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/ac1ad0ee"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the age of social media, AI, and deepfakes, discerning fact from fiction is a crucial skill. Nowadays, we’re not just getting our information from the six o’clock news. Friends, family, researchers, influencers, entertainers, news anchors, advertisers… Who can you trust?  
Timothy Caulfield, misinformation/disinformation expert, author, University of Alberta professor, and member of the Order of Canada, and Eric Rancourt, Assistant Chief Statistician at StatCan, join us to explore the challenges posed by our information environment and what can be done to counter misinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you know what your I.P. is worth?]]></title>
        <id>fcdf19a7-b9c5-4827-97b3-aa4f30205caa</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-do-you-know-what-your-ip-is-worth-_sKkcvzv"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer and IP expert Sylvain Roy discusses key considerations in IP valuation.
Explore online: 

Intellectual property valuation
Valuing Intellectual Property Assets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Sylvain Roy, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Picks for Travel Tips]]></title>
        <id>f500acdc-9c11-4358-85f2-a54b52a48045</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/top-picks-for-travel-tips"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the season or destination, safety should always be a critical part of your travel plans. From planning and preparation all the way to hotel precautions and communication procedures, we’ll review timely and relevant tips for a safe and healthy trip.
  
 Released: November 16, 2023 
  
 File Size:  3.8 MB 
  
 Length:  7:23 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sélection des meilleurs conseils de voyage]]></title>
        <id>9935658e-691c-464f-ac6c-df070e7b898a</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/slection-des-meilleurs-conseils-de-voyage"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peu importe la saison ou la destination, la sécurité devrait toujours être au cœur de vos plans de voyage. De la planification à la préparation, en passant par les précautions à prendre dans les hôtels et les procédures de communication, nous passerons en revue des conseils pertinents et pratiques pour que vous puissiez voyager en toute sécurité tout en demeurant en santé. 
  
  
 Date de diffusion : 16 novembre 16 
  
 Taille du fichier : 5 MB 
  
  Durée :  9  : 52minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 14]]></title>
        <id>6CF8D8B1-8BDC-4777-A7D9-2C6485DB1600</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/93b22bdf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T18:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that 22% or roughly one in five Canadians under the age of 34 either hadn’t heard about the Holocaust, or were unsure if they had heard about the Holocaust? In this episode, Michael Kent delves into the significance of Raczyński’s Note, a Second World War publication regarded as the first official communication with the Western Hemisphere about the atrocities of the Holocaust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to protect things that aren't formal IP rights]]></title>
        <id>ab8c6b49-0f18-4ae1-808f-43b8a9e3ff4b</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-to-protect-things-that-arent-formal-ip-rights-NumXqqc0"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seasoned IP litigator, Elizabeth Dipchand, unravels the intricacies and importance of protecting unregistered intellectual assets, managing relationships, documenting agreements and navigating the nuanced landscape where registered and unregistered rights intersect.
Explore online:

Protect new ideas and creations
Prove who owns new ideas and creations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Elizabeth Dipchand, Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 13]]></title>
        <id>156B026B-8C79-4F65-8FCB-F69463DFD49F</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/81394ed7"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T14:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we speak with Steve Moore about the most successful silent film in Canadian history, Back to God’s Country – a lusty tale of jealousy, murder and betrayal starring trailblazer Nell Shipman, Canada’s first female director. Tune in to discover why the restoration of this film received international accolades and how it projected a light on the action heroine who co-wrote and starred in this groundbreaking film.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IP saved the Canadian icon Cirque du Soleil]]></title>
        <id>45b0693e-3ebb-430a-8d23-23c3f6969c42</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-ip-saved-the-canadian-icon-cirque-du-soleil-Pi9qqByy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Lamarre, Executive Vice Chairman of the Board, Cirque du Soleil Entertainment Group, explains the critical role IP played for Cirque du Soleil during the pandemic.
Explore online:

Sample of the brands of the Cirque du Soleil
Balancing Acts: Unleashing the Power of Creativity in Your Life and Work, by Daniel Lamarre]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Daniel Lamarre, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing our Carbon Emissions]]></title>
        <id>tag:soundcloud,2010:tracks/1620053343</id>
        <link href="https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/managing-our-carbon-emissions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We, as human beings, find ourselves in a challenging situation when it comes to carbon emissions. Almost everything we do in our modern lives produces carbon emissions, which impact the very environment we live in. Is it possible to maintain our quality of life AND reduce our carbon emissions? Our scientists are working hard to address that issue. Listen to find out how.

Recommended Links:
•	Carbon Management (Natural Resources Canada) - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/our-natural-resources/energy-sources-distribution/carbon-management/4275 
•	Environment and Climate Change Canada - https://www.canada.ca/en/environment-climate-change.html 
•	Mission Innovation - http://mission-innovation.net/

Simply Science Website: www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science 
Simply Science YouTube Channel: https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fchannel%2FUCNbgD_ZfyM6lh1KbemOKfeg%3Fview_as%3Dsubscriber%253Fsub_confirmation%253D1&token=5be173-1-1594998865448
Simply Science on Twitter: https://twitter.com/NRCanScience
Simply Science on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/Simply-Science-580046026023390
Simply Science on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/simplysciencenrcan/
Simply Science on LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/company/natural-resources-canada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simply Science</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food poisoning trivia with 2 epidemiologists]]></title>
        <id>e93244ce-53df-4523-8997-0369130af1bf</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/Food-poisoning-trivia-with-2-epidemiologists-e29oj3o"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T14:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this podcast episode, we bust popular myths about food poisoning with 2 epidemiologists, Tanis Kershaw and Courtney Smith, from the Public Health Agency of Canada.
Subscribe to food recalls and alerts: https://recalls-rappels.canada.ca/en]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The food safety puzzle: piecing together an outbreak investigation]]></title>
        <id>7f18f2ac-22b7-43da-99a8-dee89f53ed59</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/The-food-safety-puzzle-piecing-together-an-outbreak-investigation-e29hb8o"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Behind every outbreak of food poisoning, a team of detectives works around the clock to pinpoint the source. This podcast episode, 4 experts from the Canadian Food Inspection Agency, Health Canada and the Public Health Agency of Canada, explain how they connect the dots to save lives.
Subscribe to food recalls and alerts: https://recalls-rappels.canada.ca/en]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the Cycle of Workplace Bullying]]></title>
        <id>9c1ab70f-40ae-4415-a3a4-686e809be60f</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/breaking-the-cycle-of-workplace-bullying-0"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite growing national conversation on violence and harassment in the workplace, bullying continues to affect many workers. CUPE’s National Health and Safety Representative, Dr. Andréane Chénier discusses how some organizations are approaching the issue.
  
Released: September 18, 2023
 File Size:  6.2 MB
 Length:  11:11 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rompre le cycle de l’intimidation au travail]]></title>
        <id>ed6b901e-f831-4fc1-8eef-6d0ad3eca8de</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/rompre-le-cycle-de-lintimidation-au-travail"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malgré des discussions de plus en plus nombreuses sur la violence et le harcèlement en milieu de travail au pays, de nombreux travailleurs continuent de vivre de l’intimidation. Andréane Chénier, représentante nationale en santé et sécurité au Syndicat canadien de la fonction publique, explique comment certains organismes abordent la question de l’intimidation sur le lieu de travail.
  
Date de diffusion : 18 septembre 2023
 Taille du fichier : 5.8 MB
 Durée : 10 : 41 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why IP is important: Insights from an IP advisor]]></title>
        <id>27e270de-97a7-4a42-b997-b9cd0c2c7c94</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/why-ip-is-important-insights-from-an-ip-advisor-3UrQd1Bo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[André Gallant, one of CIPO's IP advisors, talks about how IP advisors break myths and highlights opportunities and risks around IP and IP protection.
Explore online:

Contact CIPO IP advisors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (André Gallant, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving Change: Paving the Way for Fair Pay in Road Transportation with Mariam Abou-Dib]]></title>
        <id>013544b0-e8a1-4f28-8ebc-c5072bb3e22c</id>
        <link href="https://putting-pay-equity-into-practice.simplecast.com/episodes/driving-change-paving-the-way-for-fair-pay-in-road-transportation-jIxUS059"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, the Pay Equity Unit speaks with Mariam Abou-Dib, from Teamsters, to discuss the important role unions play in promoting pay equity within the road transportation sector and in driving positive change. By uniting for equality, the road transportation sector can continue to flourish as a crucial pillar of the global economy, benefiting workers and businesses alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>payequity-equitesalariale@chrc-ccdp.gc.ca (Teamsters Canada)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L'autoroute de l'équité salariale: Explorer les opportunités et les défis dans l'industrie du camionnage avec Josyanne Pierrat]]></title>
        <id>3a93f3cf-0d50-4e02-9383-24f3f4b89eba</id>
        <link href="https://putting-pay-equity-into-practice.simplecast.com/episodes/lautoroute-de-lequite-salariale-explorer-les-opportunites-et-les-defis-dans-lindustrie-du-camionnage-mQF7oxgm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dans cet épisode, l’Unité de l’équité salariale accueille Josyanne Pierrat de l’Association du camionnage du Québec pour discuter de l’équité salariale dans le secteur des transports. En mettant l’accent sur les industries du camionnage et de la logistique, l’épisode met en lumière les disparités existantes entre les femmes et les hommes, les défis liés à la surrèglementation, la pénurie de main-d'œuvre et le manque de représentation des femmes dans l’industrie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>payequity-equitesalariale@chrc-ccdp.gc.ca (Association du camionnage du Québec)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers: The Road to Pay Equity in the Trucking Sector with Craig Faucette]]></title>
        <id>aed297ef-721a-44b6-b0e6-992411848030</id>
        <link href="https://putting-pay-equity-into-practice.simplecast.com/episodes/breaking-barriers-the-road-to-pay-equity-in-the-trucking-sector-YjbDp5mH"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, the Pay Equity Unit meets with Craig Faucette from Trucking HR Canada to discuss some of the challenges of implementing the new Pay Equity Act in the trucking industry. We also discuss the positive impacts of achieving pay equity and how fair compensation practices can result in workplaces with improved employee satisfaction, reduced turnover, and enhanced productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>payequity-equitesalariale@chrc-ccdp.gc.ca (Trucking HR Canada)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Got 99 Problems But Being Misgendered on the Census Ain't One]]></title>
        <id>ac2bf411-78f2-4ba2-83ce-6542a886ae1b</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/cd067b8f"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies, Gentlemen, and Gentlethem! 
While every census is special, the 2021 Census was historic. It was the first to include a question about gender, making Canada the first country to collect and publish data on gender diversity from a national census. 
In this episode, we explore gender with drag king Cyril Cinder and we talk Census 2021 with StatCan’s Anne Milan. 
Join us for a new kind of gender reveal.

The Daily - Canada is the first country to provide census data on transgender and non-binary people 
Filling the gaps: Information on gender in the 2021 Census 
2021 Census: Sex at birth and gender - the whole picture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Teaser]]></title>
        <id>00e2ce99-5f9f-40ad-91a8-60b21cfd5fd0</id>
        <link href="https://putting-pay-equity-into-practice.simplecast.com/episodes/english-teaser-bKK6cAzB"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Putting Pay Equity into Practice” brings together experts and industry leaders in pay equity to help Canadian workplaces bridge the gender wage gap. Tune in to learn how you can champion pay equity in your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>payequity-equitesalariale@chrc-ccdp.gc.ca (Canadian Human Rights Commission)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bande-annonce française]]></title>
        <id>d7bfaefb-a34e-4431-90f9-5882ff40624e</id>
        <link href="https://putting-pay-equity-into-practice.simplecast.com/episodes/bande-annonce-francaise-n4QFQji3"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[« Mettre l'équité salariale en pratique » réunit des experts et des leaders du secteur de l'équité salariale afin d'aider les entreprises canadiennes à combler l'écart salarial entre les hommes et les femmes. Soyez à l'écoute pour apprendre comment vous pouvez soutenir l'équité salariale au sein de votre organisation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>payequity-equitesalariale@chrc-ccdp.gc.ca (Canadian Human Rights Commission)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 12]]></title>
        <id>37851E30-B12E-4762-9AF0-EDF8A3D3F38A</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/b28ed966"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode we speak with Krista Cooke about the curious absence of pregnant women in photos from the birth of photography in the 19th century up to the Second World War. Tune in to learn why the photo of Anna Jorosz Krista chose as her treasure is so remarkable!*re-edited version of previous release*]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Safe Workplaces for International Workers with Francy Munoz]]></title>
        <id>413d8a53-cd54-4e8a-879d-9da5003219c7</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/creating-safe-workplaces-for-international-workers-with-francy-munoz"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T19:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International workers are an integral part of the Canadian economy. There are a number of factors that make them uniquely vulnerable, from language barriers to fears around work permits and job security that may prevent them from speaking up about unsafe conditions. Francy Munoz from the C.A.R.E. for International Workers program discusses ways to improve workplace safety for international workers. 
  
Released: August 10, 2023
 File Size:  5.1 MB
 Length:  8:22 minutes
  
-------------------------
 « Creating Safe Workplaces for International Workers with Francy Munoz »
 Les travailleurs étrangers font partie intégrante de l’économie canadienne. Un certain nombre de facteurs comme les barrières linguistiques et les craintes entourant les permis de travail et la sécurité d’emploi les rendent particulièrement vulnérables et peuvent les empêcher de dénoncer des conditions dangereuses. Francy Munoz du programme C.A.R.E. for International Workers (C.A.R.E pour les travailleurs étrangers) discute de moyens d’améliorer la sécurité des travailleurs étrangers en milieu de travail.
  
Date de diffusion : 10 août 2023
 Taille du fichier : 5.1 MB
 Durée : 8 : 22 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dawson City: A Ruby in the Rough]]></title>
        <id>A664979A-4ADB-4D2B-B3E3-223705B57A02</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/6ba0002b"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T13:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In celebration of National Parks Day we have partnered with our friends at Parks Canada and have featured an episode from their wonderful new history and archaeology podcast ReCollections, in our feed. Through the remarkable lives of Madam Ruby Scott and her employees, we'll hear about Dawson's Gold Rush heyday and the boom/bust cycle of both the mining and sex work industries. At the heart of the story is Ruby's Place, an elegant false-front building conserved as part of the Klondike National Historic Sites… despite the threats from climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping Up with WHMIS]]></title>
        <id>a07a32d8-1c35-4df2-aafb-bca1abb3917e</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/keeping-up-with-whmis"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Workplace Hazardous Materials Information System has been updated. In this episode we discuss the latest changes to WHMIS and how they benefit workers and suppliers.
  
Released: July 7, 2023
 File Size: 4 MB
 Length: 6:04]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le point sur le SIMDUT]]></title>
        <id>54132f98-0f04-4db2-8cd4-cf80d6c89cb3</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/le-point-sur-le-simdut"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le Système d’information sur les matières dangereuses utilisées au travail a été mis à jour. Dans cet épisode, nous discutons des derniers changements apportés au SIMDUT et de leurs avantages pour les travailleurs et les fournisseurs.
  
Date de diffusion : 7 juillet 2023
 Taille du fichier: 4 MB
 Durée: 7 : 44]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gender Gap in Personal Protective Equipment]]></title>
        <id>1eb39e3f-90cb-4835-bf94-78a9aaffc08b</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/the-gender-gap-in-personal-protective-equipment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are consequences to a one-size-fits-all approach to personal protective equipment. In this episode, occupational and public health consultant Anya Keefe discusses the lack of representation and the need to consider gender and sex in the production and availability of personal protective equipment.
  
Released: July 7, 2023
 File Size: 7.5 MB
 Length: 13:23
  
-------------------------
  « The Gender Gap in Personal Protective Equipment »
 L’adoption d’une approche « taille unique » en matière d’équipement de protection individuelle peut avoir des conséquences. Dans cet épisode, la consultante en santé au travail et en santé publique Anya Keefe discute du manque de représentation et de la nécessité de tenir compte du genre et du sexe dans le cadre de la production et de l’offre d’équipement de protection individuelle.
  
Date de diffusion : 7 juillet, 2023
 Taille du fichier : 7.5 MB
 Durée : 13 : 23]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the unitary patent and the Unified Patent Court work]]></title>
        <id>32f1713c-b5e1-4fa7-a5f1-d63887500554</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-the-unitary-patent-and-the-unified-patent-court-work-l3steAm3"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Dearden explains how the new unitary patent and Unified Patent Court in Europe will work and shares some key considerations for anyone applying for patents in Europe.
Explore online:

Guide to the Unified Patent Court (UPC) | Gowling WLG
Unitary Patent – European Patent Office]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Gowling, Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the 40 Millionth Canadian Please Stand Up?]]></title>
        <id>750253c9-da15-4d59-b0e9-764b5a8e7a94</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/cb29d815"/>
        <updated>2023-06-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada reached an important milestone June 16, 2023. For the first time, there were 40 million people living in Canada. That means that someone out there is the 40 millionth Canadian. But who is it? 
 Laurent Martel, director of the Centre for Demography at Statistics Canada, joins us to explore what demographic data can tell us about this person, as well as the implications of Canada’s changing demographics and its rapid population growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Inclusive Workplaces for Trans and Non-binary Workers with Dani Gomez-Ortega]]></title>
        <id>2a498126-d637-42b2-9986-cd66bf9a5cfc</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/creating-safe-inclusive-workplaces-for-trans-and-non-binary-workers-with-dani-gomez-ortega"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T19:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways employers can make the workplace safer and more inclusive for trans and non-binary employees, from educating workers on trans issues and human rights, to ensuring access to gender-neutral washrooms. In this episode, diversity and inclusion champion Dani Gomez-Ortega discusses why inclusive workplaces matter, roles and responsibilities, and the huge impact kindness can make.
  
Released: June 13, 2023
 File Size:  8.6 MB
 Length:  14:52 minutes
  
-------------------------
 Title: « Creating Inclusive Workplaces for Trans and Non-binary Workers »
 Les employeurs peuvent utiliser de nombreux moyens pour rendre le lieu de travail plus sûr et plus inclusif pour les employés trans et non binaires, notamment en sensibilisant les travailleurs aux questions trans et aux droits de la personne, ou en garantissant l’accès à des toilettes mixtes. Dans cet épisode, Dani Gomez-Ortega, championne de la diversité et de l’inclusion, explique pourquoi les lieux de travail inclusifs sont importants, quels sont les rôles et les responsabilités et quelle incidence la gentillesse peut avoir.
  
Date de diffusion : 13 juin 2023
 Taille du fichier : 8.6 MB
  Durée : 14 : 52 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The gold standard of mineral exploration]]></title>
        <id>tag:soundcloud,2010:tracks/1537893031</id>
        <link href="https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/the-gold-standard-of-mineral-exploration"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know metals like gold, copper and nickel are essential to our way of life. Metals are used in just about everything. So how do we make sure that we have a continuous supply of these metals? How do you find new ore deposits to make sure we meet future demand? Our scientists are working hard to specifically address that issue. Listen to find out how.

Recommended Links:
•	Geological Survey of Canada - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/science-and-data/research-centres-and-labs/geological-survey-canada/17100 
•	Geoscientists Canada - https://geoscientistscanada.ca/ 
•	Prospector and Developers Association of Canada - https://www.pdac.ca/ 
•	Quebec Mineral Exploration Association - https://aemq.org/en/

Simply Science Website: www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science 
Simply Science YouTube Channel: https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fchannel%2FUCNbgD_ZfyM6lh1KbemOKfeg%3Fview_as%3Dsubscriber%253Fsub_confirmation%253D1&token=5be173-1-1594998865448
Simply Science on Twitter: https://twitter.com/NRCanScience
Simply Science on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/Simply-Science-580046026023390
Simply Science on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/simplysciencenrcan/
Simply Science on LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/company/natural-resources-canada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simply Science</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to apply for a patent in the U.S. and other countries.]]></title>
        <id>3d0ea191-8332-4f8b-afd5-3b6fb150a98b</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-to-apply-for-a-patent-in-the-us-and-other-countries-mYV_vbuK"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Lambert, Patent agent at Bereskin & Parr explains how the provisional patent in the US works and how to apply for patent protection abroad using the PCT. 
 
Explore online: Provisional Application for Patent | USPTO (English only)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 11]]></title>
        <id>71275AE6-C1E8-47E4-9031-2F4A8A210C26</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/5d274a4d"/>
        <updated>2023-05-10T13:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Hood was only 24 in 1821, when he participated in the 1st of the infamous Franklin Expeditions. Hood was to take navigational, geographical and meteorological observations, and to make drawings of the land and of various objects of natural history. Unfortunately, Hood would not live to see his paintings published in Franklin’s account. In this episode LAC Archivist Shane McCord tells us about the tragic story of Robert Hood and the treasures he left behind, which are now part of the LAC collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips to Navigate the Brave New Workplace]]></title>
        <id>772cf722-cbe3-4fd6-b8af-5cab321469d0</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/tips-to-navigate-the-brave-new-workplace"/>
        <updated>2023-05-09T20:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing small changes can have a profound effect on employee well-being. Leadership expert Dr. Julian Barling shares the most important factors for creating a productive, healthy and safe workplace. Dr. Barling will speak more about navigating the brave new workplace at CCOHS Forum, taking place September 26-27 in Halifax, Nova Scotia.
  
Released: May 9, 2023
 File Size:  6.7 MB
 Length:  11:30 minutes
  
-------------------------
 « Comment retrouver le Nord dans le nouveau monde du travail? »
 Description: La mise en œuvre de petits changements peut avoir un effet profond sur le bien-être des employés. L’expert en leadership Julian Barling, Ph. D., nous présente aujourd’hui les incontournables de la création d’un milieu de travail productif, sain et sécuritaire. M. Barling nous expliquera mieux comment retrouver le Nord dans le nouveau monde du travail lors du Forum du CCHST, qui aura lieu du 26 au 27 septembre à Halifax, en Nouvelle-Écosse.
  
Date de diffusion : 9 mai 2023
 Taille du fichier : 6.7 MB
 Durée : 11 : 30 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How not to spend money on bad patents]]></title>
        <id>ca5eac4f-008b-43b8-9cd3-4587e255323e</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-not-to-spend-money-on-bad-patents-WQDakG_k"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Carbonneau, patent broker who evaluates hundreds of patents for clients each year shares some tips and tricks on where to spend the money to ensure you file for valuable IP rights. 
Explore online: 
Louis Carbonneau’s blog
 
(English only)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Louis Carbonneau, Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the dates on our food]]></title>
        <id>d6799733-40d3-4106-9c99-b209ffea6716</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/Understanding-the-dates-on-our-food-e22vfh2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've finally gathered the courage to clean up your fridge or pantry, but how do you know what to keep or chuck? In this podcast, labelling expert Laura Reid helps us understand the different dates on our foods.
We also hear from Sophie Langlois-Blouin, Vice-President of RECYC Québec, about food waste in Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In a Movie About the Economy, Is Inflation the Bad Guy?]]></title>
        <id>a593b0a3-6a24-49c9-809c-8a3e0f0d5f58</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/9dbaf1c4"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StatCan’s Consumer Price Index tells us a lot about the economy… if you know what to look for.  
Guy Gellatly, Chief Economic Advisor at StatCan, joins us at the mic to break down the CPI and answer our questions about the economy. What’s the ideal inflation rate? Is no inflation the best kind of inflation? And what is a deflationary spiral?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing ReCollections: A Parks Canada Podcast]]></title>
        <id>2d604408-bc61-11ed-a6d0-371b77f9b71d</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for a journey of national historic significance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L’Anse aux Meadows: The Saga of Vinland]]></title>
        <id>8bf54926-d8c9-11ed-91d3-ffd80f910e57</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Travel back to the Viking Age to uncover the remnants of a thousand-year-old Norse encampment. We’ll hear about their incredible journey from Greenland to northern Newfoundland from a diverse group of experts including historians, archaeologists, and interpreters at L’Anse aux Meadows National Historic Site.

Learn more: 

L’Anse aux Meadows National Historic Site: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/nl/meadows 

Google Arts and Culture Exhibition: https://g.co/arts/zsrgMj8ex1cQe5yK7


Plan your visit: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/nl/meadows/visit 

UNESCO page: https://whc.unesco.org/en/list/4/


National Film Board documentaries:

The Man Who Discovered America: https://www.nfb.ca/film/man_discovered_america 

The Vinland Mystery: https://www.nfb.ca/film/vinland_mystery/



Do you have a suggestion for a new National Historic Person, Site or Event? We’d love to hear it! Visit https://parks.canada.ca/commemorate for details on how to submit a nomination.
A transcript and bibliography for this episode is available on our website: https://parks.canada.ca/recollections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dawson City: A Ruby in the Rough]]></title>
        <id>57b1d404-d8c9-11ed-b188-ff1aa21b7b9a</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ruby's Place in Dawson City, Yukon, “the Paris of the North.” Through the remarkable lives of Madam Ruby Scott and her employees, we’ll hear about Dawson’s Gold Rush heyday and the boom/bust cycle of both the mining and sex work industries. At the heart of the story is Ruby's Place, an elegant false-front building conserved as part of the Klondike National Historic Sites… despite the threats from climate change.

Learn More: 

Klondike National Historic Sites: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/yt/klondike


Plan your visit: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/yt/klondike/visit


Google Arts and Culture Exhibition: https://artsandculture.google.com/story/PwWxfnGFmjSquw


UNESCO World Heritage Site (Tentative List): https://whc.unesco.org/en/tentativelists/6255/


Tr'ochëk National Historic Site: https://www.pc.gc.ca/apps/dfhd/page_nhs_eng.aspx?id=1970&i=65024



The Other Little House: The Brothel as a Colonial Institution on the Canadian Prairies, 1880–93 by L. K. Bertram: https://academic.oup.com/jsh/article/56/1/58/6554394?login=false



Do you have a suggestion for a new National Historic Person, Site or Event? We’d love to hear it! Visit https://parks.canada.ca/commemorate for details on how to submit a nomination.
A transcript and bibliography for this episode is available on our website: https://parks.canada.ca/recollections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gwaii Haanas: The Living Landscapes of SG̱ang Gwaay]]></title>
        <id>aed14ba2-d8c9-11ed-8369-e70ff95c3d55</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’ll travel to the Pacific Northwest islands of Haida Gwaii, home to the Haida Nation for more than 13,000 years. Our focus: a collaborative archaeology project at an evacuated village on the remote island of SGang Gwaay, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, that was devastated by hurricane-force winds in a 2018 storm. Many voices tell the rich history of Gwaii Haanas National Park Reserve, National Marine Conservation Area Reserve and Haida Heritage Site. 
Special thanks to Consulting Producer Camille Collinson.

Learn More:

Gwaii Haanas National Park Reserve, National Marine Conservation Area Reserve and Haida Heritage Site: https://parks.canada.ca/pn-np/bc/gwaiihaanas


Living Landscapes of SG̱ang Gwaay project: https://parks.canada.ca/pn-np/bc/gwaiihaanas/nature/conservation/restauration-restoration/vivants-living


Follow the Gwaii Haanas - Islands of Beauty Facebook page for the latest on the Living Landscapes project: https://www.facebook.com/GwaiiHaanas/


Plan your visit: https://parks.canada.ca/pn-np/bc/gwaiihaanas/visit


UNESCO World Heritage Site: https://whc.unesco.org/en/list/157/


Take the Haida Gwaii Pledge: https://haidagwaiipledge.ca/


The Hope For Wellness Helpline is available at 1-855-242-3310 or https://www.hopeforwellness.ca/  


Do you have a suggestion for a new National Historic Person, Site or Event? We’d love to hear it! Visit https://parks.canada.ca/commemorate for details on how to submit a nomination.
A transcript and bibliography for this episode is available on our website: https://parks.canada.ca/recollections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grosse Île: The Quarantine Island]]></title>
        <id>7d5ef3bc-d8c9-11ed-8710-43f547fcd7db</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For over a century, an unassuming island in the St. Lawrence River played a major role in the immigration journey from Europe to North America. A scene of hope and tragedy, punctuated by a series of deadly crises, Grosse Île was home to a quarantine station that served as the gateway for millions of newcomers. Witness to pandemics, health emergencies and the development of modern medical science, Grosse Île and the Irish Memorial National Historic Site is a powerful reminder of the immigrant experience. And it all kicked off with a volcanic eruption on the other side of the planet.

Learn More:

Grosse-Ile and the Irish Memorial National Historic Site: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/qc/grosseile


Plan Your Visit: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/qc/grosseile/visit


Dr. Frédérick Montizambert, National Historic Person: https://www.pc.gc.ca/apps/DFHD/page_nhs_eng.aspx?id=1843



For the Temporary Accommodation of Settlers by David Monteyne: https://www.mqup.ca/for-the-temporary-accommodation-of-settlers-products-9780228006381.php


Google Arts and Culture Exhibition: https://artsandculture.google.com/story/WgXRiCleYInljA



Do you have a suggestion for a new National Historic Person, Site or Event? We’d love to hear it! Visit https://parks.canada.ca/commemorate for details on how to submit a nomination.
A transcript and bibliography for this episode is available on our website: https://parks.canada.ca/recollections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louisbourg: Enslavement and Freedom at the French Fortress]]></title>
        <id>9db57c30-d8c9-11ed-b49f-17653b65c0b1</id>
        <link href="https://parks.canada.ca/recollections"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we find traces of the lives of enslaved people at the 18th-century French Fortress of Louisbourg in Cape Breton, Nova Scotia. By piecing together the unique story of Guinea-born Marie Marguerite Rose, we’ll learn about those who lived and died in enslavement…as well as the rise and fall (and rise again) of the Fortress of Louisbourg National Historic Site.
Special thanks to our Consulting Producers: Dr. Karolyn Smardz-Frost and Dr. Afua Cooper of A Black People’s History of Canada Project: https://www.blackpeopleshistory.ca/
Learn More:

Fortress of Louisbourg National Historic Site: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/ns/louisbourg


Marie Marguerite Rose, National Historic Person: https://www.pc.gc.ca/apps/dfhd/page_nhs_eng.aspx?id=12005


Plan your visit: https://parks.canada.ca/lhn-nhs/ns/louisbourg/visit


Google Arts and Culture Exhibit: https://artsandculture.google.com/story/vQVxpt_04-996g



Do you have a suggestion for a new National Historic Person, Site or Event? We’d love to hear it! Visit https://parks.canada.ca/commemorate for details on how to submit a nomination.
A transcript and bibliography for this episode is available on our website: https://parks.canada.ca/recollections]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Mason: Wilderness Artist - from Discover Library and Archives Canada podcast]]></title>
        <id>513f89e2-5f09-11ee-a4d6-cf2b15d7183f</id>
        <link href="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/Pages/podcasts.aspx"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T20:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A special episode from our friends at the Discover Library and Archives Canada podcast - Bill Mason: Wilderness Artist.
If you enjoyed our ReCollections episode Grosse-Île: The Quarantine Island, check out their The Shamrock and the Fleur-de-Lys episode to learn more about Irish immigration to Québec.
Bill Mason's films: Pukaskwa National Park and Paddle to the Sea.
Plan a visit to Pukaskwa National Park in Ontario.
Discover Library and Archives Canada podcast is available wherever you get your podcasts. Subscribe for lots more stories about the treasures in their collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ReCollections</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day of Mourning: Donna Van Bruggen’s Story]]></title>
        <id>5f833c62-57b0-478a-9942-358702a9e7e4</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/day-of-mourning-donna-van-bruggens-story"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“He had big hands, big feet, and a great big heart.” Donna Van Bruggen’s life was forever changed the day her son David didn’t come home from work. Hear her powerful story, and how getting involved with Threads of Life has helped her process her grief.
  
 ·         Released:  April 12, 2023
  ·         File Size:   9.9 MB
  ·         Length:  18:29 minutes
  
 *************************
  « Day of Mourning: Donna Van Bruggen’s Story »
 « Il avait de grandes mains, de grands pieds et un grand cœur. » La vie de Donna Van Bruggen a basculé le jour où son fils David n’est pas rentré du travail. Écoutez son histoire émouvante et découvrez comment sa participation à Fil de vie l’a aidée à surmonter son chagrin.
  
 ·         Date de diffusion : 12 avril 2023
  ·         Taille du fichier :  9.9 MB
   Durée :  18 : 29 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The peacekeeping series - Africa: The Congo]]></title>
        <id>https://blubrry.com/facesoffreedom//the-peacekeeping-series-africa-the-congo/</id>
        <link href="https://blubrry.com/facesoffreedom/80217691/the-peacekeeping-series-africa-the-congo/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Hamel first joined the Canadian Armed Forces in 1973, and went on to serve for more than 42 years, between the regular and reserve forces. He served on Operation Crocodile in the Congo in 2003.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veterans Affairs Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workplace Impacts from Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>9efc7b55-8073-44ef-b099-f89b96116458</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/workplace-impacts-from-climate-change"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada is warming at roughly twice the rate of the rest of the world, and the effects are being felt in workplaces across the country. In the latest episode of Health and Safety To Go, hear from a geoscientist and climate change expert on which industries are most affected and how employers and workers can adapt.
  
Released: March 9, 2023
 File Size: 3.6 MB
 Length: 6:41 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effets des changements climatiques dans les milieux de travail]]></title>
        <id>932c1a43-9474-4f3d-bb8b-f8c843899620</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/effets-des-changements-climatiques-dans-les-milieux-de-travail"/>
        <updated>2023-03-09T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Au Canada, le réchauffement climatique est environ deux fois plus rapide que dans le reste du monde, et les effets de celui-ci se font sentir jusque dans les milieux de travail partout au pays. Dans le plus récent balado De la SST pour emporter!, un géoscientifique et spécialiste en changements climatiques explique quels sont les secteurs les plus touchés et comment les employeurs et les travailleurs peuvent s’adapter.
  
Date de diffusion : 9 mars 2023
 Taille du fichier : 3.5 MB
 Durée : 6 : 49 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who owns AI-generated creations (and why you should care)]]></title>
        <id>57215d48-582d-49ea-80ef-a5a999755c35</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/who-owns-ai-generated-creations-and-why-you-should-care-ZPe51mNa"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guillaume Lavoie Ste-Marie, copyright, patent and trademark litigator and principal at Smart & Biggar in Montreal, talks about ChatGPT, intellectual property (IP) tips and traps that artificial intelligence (AI) users should be aware of before creating works with AI—and if using AI to answer IP questions is a good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Guillaume Lavoie Ste-Marie, Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A heated conversation on heat pumps]]></title>
        <id>tag:soundcloud,2010:tracks/1447027255</id>
        <link href="https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/a-heated-conversation-on-heat-pumps"/>
        <updated>2023-02-21T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing quite like a Canadian winter. Majestic scenery, fun outdoor activities, and brutally cold days that cause your heating bill to skyrocket. Scientists and engineers at Natural Resources Canada believe a promising technology can help reduce your energy consumption, the heat pump. On this episode: What are heat pumps? How do they work? Why is everyone talking about them? Are they right for you? Listen to find out.

Recommended Links:
•	Heating and Cooling With a Heat Pump - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/energy-efficiency/energy-star-canada/about/energy-star-announcements/publications/heating-and-cooling-heat-pump/6817 
•	Adapting Heat Pumps to Our Canadian Climate (Simply Science Video) - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=276AP6Uh5nU 
•	The future of home heating: Hybrid home heating systems offer energy savings and reduce GHG emissions (Simply Science Article) - https://natural-resources.canada.ca/simply-science/the-future-home-heating-hybrid-home-heating-systems-offer-energy-savings-and-reduce-g/22236 

Simply Science Website: www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science 
Simply Science YouTube Channel: https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fchannel%2FUCNbgD_ZfyM6lh1KbemOKfeg%3Fview_as%3Dsubscriber%253Fsub_confirmation%253D1&token=5be173-1-1594998865448
Simply Science on Twitter: https://twitter.com/NRCanScience
Simply Science on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/Simply-Science-580046026023390
Simply Science on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/simplysciencenrcan/
Simply Science on LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/company/natural-resources-canada]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simply Science</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your IP future-proof? How to think like an in-house IP counsel]]></title>
        <id>c68137a4-cf51-4ced-bf32-77d853e3f438</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/is-your-ip-future-proof-how-to-think-like-an-in-house-ip-counsel-JRDPNKwy"/>
        <updated>2023-02-01T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Guay, director of IP at Shopify, shares some ideas and insights on how to think like a pro when it comes to patents.
Explore online:

Plan for success – Build an IP strategy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Tips for Improving Workplace Safety with Plain Language]]></title>
        <id>95f1e130-a234-4f9e-8dc6-c304585d7b13</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/four-tips-for-improving-workplace-safety-with-plain-language"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T17:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are jargon and acronyms used everywhere in your workplace? Create a safer and more inclusive environment by using plain language. Here are four tips to get started.
  
Released: January 27, 2023
 File Size: 3 MB
 Length: 5:03 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quatre conseils pour améliorer la sécurité sur le lieu de travail grâce à un langage simple]]></title>
        <id>56483146-230d-4d5f-82f1-c965c3a5175d</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/quatre-conseils-pour-amliorer-la-scurit-sur-le-lieu-de-travail-grce-un-langage-simple"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T17:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Utilisez-vous du jargon et des acronymes partout dans votre lieu de travail? Adoptez un langage simple pour créer un environnement plus sûr et plus inclusif. Voici quatre conseils pour commencer.
  
Date de diffusion : 27 janvier 2023
 Taille du fichier : 3.3 MB
 Durée : 6 : 35 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 9]]></title>
        <id>12AF848A-8BA5-4AEF-A980-6BBC3D1F13AA</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/45900a7c"/>
        <updated>2023-01-18T16:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 9th episode of Treasures Revealed, LAC Curator Forrest Pass unravels the mystery of a Masonic tracing board dating back to the early 1800s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IP rights saved my business]]></title>
        <id>7911ec6f-9b5c-449e-942f-b791c219416c</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-ip-rights-saved-my-business-WYQDyrSs"/>
        <updated>2023-01-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johanne Boivin, expert advisor at Point Cardinal and former CEO or Executive Vice-President shares her story how IP saved her business.
Explore online :
Learn about IP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Point Cardinal, CIPO)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turning manure into gold]]></title>
        <id>3513bd14-368b-463c-a03c-df97430ed169</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/eb9844f8"/>
        <updated>2022-12-15T17:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Waste is not waste. It’s just misplaced resources”. That is according to Rajinikanth Rajagopal and the team of researchers at the Sherbrooke Research and Development Centre as they work to adapt anaerobic bio digestion to a Canadian climate and livestock sector.  We also speak to Mauricio Alanís, Director of Sustainability Strategy and Partnerships at Maple Leaf Foods. His company is interested in the technology and AAFC’s expertise as it could all play an important role in Maple Leaf Foods’ sustainability journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temps down, heads up: Working Safely in the Cold]]></title>
        <id>cda728cd-e607-4b35-b228-ffa467342c79</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/temps-down-heads-up-working-safely-in-the-cold"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T22:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a lot more to working safely in the cold than bundling up in layers. In the latest CCOHS podcast: what workers and employers need to know.
  
Released: December 13, 2022
 File Size: 5 MB
 Length: 6:34 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Températures à la baisse ? Attachez votre tuque ! Travaillez au froid en sécurité]]></title>
        <id>6833ea75-ff40-4bfb-9f2b-3902d0c66a60</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/tempratures-la-baisse-attachez-votre-tuque-travaillez-au-froid-en-scurit"/>
        <updated>2022-12-13T22:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pour travailler en toute sécurité dans le froid, il ne suffit pas de s’emmitoufler dans plusieurs couches de vêtements. Dans le dernier balado du CCHST : ce que les travailleurs et les employeurs doivent savoir.
  
Date de diffusion : 13 decembre 2022
 Taille du fichier :5 MB
 Durée : 9 : 13 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are crickets the new tofu?]]></title>
        <id>6a55cf10-9370-4e00-84d4-81ad930203aa</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/Are-crickets-the-new-tofu-e1rtvhc"/>
        <updated>2022-12-08T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crickets have attracted global interest for their sustainable farming potential. And yet, so few of us have hopped on to this protein trend. In this podcast, we explore the edible insect landscape in Canada with food trend expert Dana McCauley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA World Cup special: How FIFA protects its intellectual property]]></title>
        <id>7f9de9c0-3238-4aaa-958d-535b71b43472</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/fifa-world-cup-special-how-fifa-protects-its-intellectual-property-d0ihJoDR"/>
        <updated>2022-12-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julie Jones and Raed AlHout explain how the FIFA head office in Switzerland and officials in Qatar protect FIFA IP assets before and during the World Cup.
Explore online: 
FIFA Intellectual Property Guidelines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (FIFA, Raed AlHout, Julie Jones, CIPO)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 8]]></title>
        <id>8A54F9C1-40A1-4BAE-AFBB-BFA7975810DB</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/5ae8a8ec"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T14:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Treasures Revealed, Indigenous Research Archivist Elizabeth Montour relies on knowledge and instinct to decipher the story of a Kanienhkenha:ka woman she observes in a 19th century watercolour. As Elizabeth examines the painting, she imagines what life might have been like for her ancestors living in her home of Kahnawake, in a time of great transition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modelling the future of water]]></title>
        <id>19c37a2e-ecb3-46dc-b759-6700d0492e42</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/f5f619ce"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To predict the future of water, we have to understand the present. That's exactly what AAFC's Dr. David Lapen and Dr. Steven Frey from Aquanty Inc., are endeavoring to do. Listen in as they discuss their work on a complex, country-wide hydrological modelling tool.  It is designed to help researchers, producers and decision makers anticipate water resources of tomorrow and make better, more informed decisions today. This is the Canada 1 Water project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Houses, Not Gases]]></title>
        <id>5f2deeb9-f66b-4207-ad18-5cd3d2927619</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/03fe14f0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada is facing both a climate crisis and a housing crisis, and they are interconnected. 
Choices we make about our homes impact the environment: their location and how much we need to use a car to get around, the heat source that they use, the materials used in their construction. 
At the same time, the climate impacts our homes: when severe weather strikes and causes damage to our homes, we have no choice but to rebuild, and even if we escape unscathed, we still have to decide how much to change our lifestyles to adapt to a changing climate. 
Andrew DeFazio, Climate Change Advisor at Canada Mortgage and Housing Corporation (CMHC) joins us to explore how we can climate-proof our housing strategy and home-proof our climate strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carer-Friendly Workplaces]]></title>
        <id>c050d323-3a64-442c-9777-adb7a1ecad98</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/carer-friendly-workplaces-with-nora-spinx"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T17:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of workers in Canada who are also caregivers is on the rise. Here’s how workplaces can provide support.
  
Released: November 16, 2022
 File Size: 9 MB
 Length: 17:57 minutes
  
-------------------------
 >
  Le nombre de travailleurs canadiens qui sont également des aidants naturels augmente. Voici comment les lieux de travail peuvent vous aider.
  
Date de diffusion : 16 novembre 2022
 Taille du fichier :9 MB
 Durée : 17 : 57 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 7]]></title>
        <id>C4563021-5A44-47B1-BDD4-084C4554022D</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/c6508cd6"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T20:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 7th episode of Treasures Revealed we speak with Senior Archivist Christine Barrass about an extraordinary scroll, or Sefer Torah, that is part of the Shearith Israel synagogue collection held at LAC. This scroll is a document  hand-written in Hebrew by a scribe and measures approximately 35 metres in length when fully unrolled. The Sefer Torah is considered to be the most valued object in Judaism, and is a highlight of the Jewish collections at LAC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You asked, we answer]]></title>
        <id>a57e62a4-073a-4f61-89e3-638d818c169a</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/You-asked--we-answer-e1q38vh"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, we asked for your questions. This podcast, we answer them! We reached out to experts across the country to get answers about travelling with food, alcohol labelling, pet food, chicken hatcheries, allergen recalls and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the difference between a corporation name, trade name, brand name and domain name?]]></title>
        <id>0617f558-97ad-47cb-8260-481324ff59bd</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/what-is-the-difference-between-a-corporation-name-trade-name-brand-name-and-domain-name-8ahjiPVK"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Lacelle from Corporations Canada and lawyer James Plotkin clarify the differences between and importance of legal/trade/brand/domain names.
Explore online:

Corporations Canada
Incorporating in a specific province or territory
Filing for a trademark with the Canadian Intellectual Property Office
Canadian Internet Registration Authority]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (James Plotkin, CIPO, Corporations Canada)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prenez position contre les risques ergonomiques]]></title>
        <id>320bbda9-f11b-4a9d-a251-e69d507e64ef</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prenez-position-contre-les-risques-ergonomiques"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T22:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La prévention des blessures ergonomiques commence par la détermination des dangers et des facteurs de risque. Voici ce qu'il faut surveiller lorsqu'il s'agit de se tenir au travail.
  
Date de diffusion : 20 octobre 2022
 Taille du fichier : 4.8 MB
 Durée : 9 : 23 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take a Stand on Ergonomic Hazards]]></title>
        <id>3b949531-0016-4c99-8992-e106be58e237</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/take-a-stand-on-ergonomic-hazards"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing any ergonomic injury starts with identifying the hazards and risk factors. Here’s what to look out for when it comes to standing on the job.
  
Released: October 19, 2022
 File Size: 5 MB
 Length: 6:40 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasures Revealed: Episode 6]]></title>
        <id>6ED40A00-CBCA-4FD9-A464-8E5D8831C717</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/f5ae1610"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Treasures Revealed, we speak with Marcelle Cinq-Mars, senior military archivist in the Government Archives Division at LAC. Marcelle tells us about the amazing discovery she made while rehousing documents LAC received from the Department of National Defence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Library and Archives Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Haven't We Ended Poverty Yet?]]></title>
        <id>49968a23-9f00-483c-927e-120f6842f8a8</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/e54f3612"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It used to be that Statistics Canada didn’t measure poverty. Not exactly. Poverty is complex, and there wasn't a single definition that everyone agreed on. So while StatCan did measure low income and other income inequality indicators, it didn't measure poverty per se. That is, until 2018, when the government chose to use the Market Basket Measure, or MBM, as Canada's Official Poverty Line. That means that the government now uses the MBM to track its poverty reduction targets.  
 
But something strange happened during the pandemic: in 2020 the poverty rate fell. And it fell quite a bit. In fact, the poverty rate dropped in one year almost as much as it had in the four preceding years.
 
But why? What happened? Will the poverty rate continue to fall? And what happens if it hits zero? How would health outcomes change? Education outcomes? People's general happiness and well-being? 
 
Has there ever been a time and place in Canada where the poverty rate was zero? The closest may be the Mincome Experiment of the 1970s in Manitoba.   Many Canadians have never heard of this guaranteed income experiment, but it offers a glimpse at what eliminating poverty might look like. 
 
To learn more, we spoke with Burton Gustajtis an economist from Statistics Canada, Evelyn Forget, a Professor of Economics and Community Health Sciences at the University of Manitoba and Kevin Milligan, a Professor of Economics in the Vancouver School of Economics at the University of British Columbia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sylvia Ostry: Lessons from a Legend]]></title>
        <id>4e87cd5d-8c66-444a-8b47-9319c72d145f</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/26b274b8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If this is the first time you’re hearing about Sylvia Ostry, buckle up. 
Sylvia was appointed Canada’s first and only female Chief Statistician in 1972, but she didn’t get there by playing by the rules. She was ambitious but grew up in a world where many thought that it was shameful to be female and have a career. 
 
Sylvia was a Jewish woman in economics, and even after she earned a Ph.D. from the University of Cambridge, she was denied a job with the United Nations because of her gender. Nevertheless, she had a storied career, becoming the Chairman of the Economic Council of Canada then the Chief Economist  at the OECD. But we're not focusing on her career highlights. We're going behind the scenes to look at how she challenged herself to succeed, becoming both a respected economist and mother, and how she handled setbacks, and discrimination, all while staying true to herself and demonstrating the integrity for which she's remembered today.
We’re celebrating the 50th anniversary of Sylvia Ostry’s appointment as Chief Statistician. In this episode of Eh Sayers, featuring interviews with her sons, Adam Ostry and Jonathan Ostry, we are pleased to introduce you to this remarkable woman and to share with you eight pieces of advice inspired by her life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Statistics Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do incubators/accelerators support innovators and their IP?]]></title>
        <id>9f1c96a4-d660-4816-91ce-6632a3538eda</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-do-incubators-accelerators-support-innovators-and-their-ip-6wiuPD_f"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josée Pharand, Director of IP Programs and Policies at ventureLAB, explains how ventureLAB supports innovators and their IP in the Canadian innovation ecosystem. Tune in for a discussion about choosing between patents and trade secrets, and learn how many accelerators and incubators help companies grow without asking for any stake in their IP, equity or future revenues.
Discover online: https://www.venturelab.ca/news/intellectual-property-101]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (Josée Pharand, ventureLAB)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indigenous Perspectives on Health and Safety]]></title>
        <id>c1b2b275-60a4-4157-ada0-a5442de330f8</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/indigenous-perspectives-on-health-and-safety"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In First Nations communities, several factors are considered before undertaking new health and safety initiatives. Jeff Robert, an Indigenous human resources practitioner, shares his insights in this episode.
  
Released: September 21, 2022
 File Size: 5.5 MB
 Length: 9:57 minutes
  
>
 Dans les communautés des Premières Nations, plusieurs facteurs sont pris en considération avant de lancer de nouvelles initiatives en matière de santé et de sécurité. Jeff Robert, un conseiller en ressources humaines autochtone, présente ses points de vue dans cet épisode.
  
Date de diffusion : 21 septembre 2022
 Taille du fichier : 5.5 MB
 Durée : 9 : 57 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving our organic soils]]></title>
        <id>814c8431-c3b0-44be-9b66-9c97f0ddb649</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/1e1f16a5"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[40% of Quebec’s fruits and vegetables are grown in the Montérégie region due to its abundantly fertile organic soils. But these soils are under threat. We speak to Jacynthe Masse, an agroecology researcher, and Denys Van Winden, a vegetable producer from Sherrington, to learn about the challenges they’re facing and the experiments they’re running to save these soils.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Three Basic Rights of Workers]]></title>
        <id>d3ce3438-d32d-4e1f-9131-cc8d6aac0619</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/comprendre-les-trois-droits-fondamentaux-des-travailleurs-0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T12:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description: Every person employed in Canada has the right to a safe work environment. In this episode we discuss the three basic rights of all workers in Canada.
  
Released: August 16, 2022
 File Size: 4.2 MB
 Length: 6 : 13 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comprendre les trois droits fondamentaux des travailleurs]]></title>
        <id>fb389f8e-c5cd-4da5-9121-891b3c498e5f</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/comprendre-les-trois-droits-fondamentaux-des-travailleurs"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T12:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toute personne employée au Canada a droit à un milieu de travail sécuritaire. Dans le présent épisode, nous discutons des trois droits fondamentaux de tous les travailleurs au Canada.
  
Date de diffusion : 16 août 2022
 Taille du fichier :2 MB
 Durée : 8 : 20 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disconnecting from Work]]></title>
        <id>cc3381fd-6699-467b-8508-4aa36a583bee</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/disconnecting-from-work"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to fully disconnect from work is key to a healthy, happy, and productive workplace. In this episode, we discuss what employers and workers can each do to help.
  
Released: July 19, 2022
 File Size:  3 MB
 Length: 5:51 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Se déconnecter du travail]]></title>
        <id>933fcd6b-0ff4-4b13-a9c8-7be175f0b65b</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/se-dconnecter-du-travail"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Être capable de complètement décrocher du travail est essentiel à un milieu de travail sain, positif et productif. Dans cet épisode, nous discutons de ce que les employeurs et les employés peuvent faire pour aider.
  
Date de diffusion : 17 juillet 2022
 Taille du fichier :7 MB
 Durée : 7 : 24 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agroforestry: The new-old science]]></title>
        <id>ce67d808-7ad5-40ca-b045-86b09b372234</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/782b35a9"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When agriculture meets forestry, the result can have a surprising impact on the environment, wildlife habitats, crop production, and beyond. AAFC research scientist Dr. Raju Soolanayakanahally and Kevin Boon, General Manager of the BC Cattlemen’s Association, explore the roots of the long-standing practice of agroforestry, and the benefits it brings to the future of agriculture and climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling the sting: the impact of honey fraud on beekeepers]]></title>
        <id>b65ad5a3-70a7-4eed-a5fa-62b52248b01f</id>
        <link href="https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/cfia/episodes/Feeling-the-sting-the-impact-of-honey-fraud-on-beekeepers-e1k8puh"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a sticky situation out there. In this podcast, we discuss honey adulteration with Jake Berg, a Saskatchewanian beekeeper, and Carmen Leung, a policy and program leader at the CFIA.
This episode is a collaboration on adulterated honey with Agriculture and Agri-Food Canada’s podcast, The First Sixteen. Bee sure to catch their episode as well: 
https://agriculture.agr.gc.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast/first-sixteen-podcast-ep-021]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Canadian Food Inspection Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shedding light on food fraud]]></title>
        <id>415f0ab2-69e7-42a1-a062-4bb6f41c4024</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/3aeabd91"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agriculture and Agri-Food Canada and the Canadian Food Inspection Agency come together in this special two-part episode on honey fraud in Canada. Hear a scientist from each organization discuss how they identify fraudulent products – and listen to the CFIA’s Inspect and Protect episode here for the perspective of a policy leader and a beekeeper!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How  traditional brands and IP rights are entering the metaverse]]></title>
        <id>7b19c1eb-3b25-4680-b4cc-1941992d0eec</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-traditional-brands-and-ip-rights-are-entering-the-metaverse-nRvjjt1y"/>
        <updated>2022-06-22T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brigitte Chan, lawyer and trademark agent discusses  what the IP professionals are observing as real brands are going virtual in a fictional universe; the metaverse.
 
Discover online: 
The IP Metaverse Series: Part I: Brands are Plugging in and Cashing in - Protecting Trademarks and Copyright in Virtual Goods and Services
Part II: IP Metaverse Series - Part II: Patent Considerations
 
The IP Metaverse Series -– Part II: Patent Considerations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying and Monitoring Trends in Occupational Disease]]></title>
        <id>361508d0-9a22-4e5c-8078-4bdda713dd1f</id>
        <link href="https://ccohs.libsyn.com/identifying-and-monitoring-trends-in-occupational-disease"/>
        <updated>2022-06-14T16:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking patterns and trends in occupational disease in different industries can help target prevention efforts. We talk with Paul Demers from the Occupational Cancer Research Centre about the Occupational Disease Surveillance System (ODSS) and what the data reveals.
  
Released: June 14, 2022
 File Size:  5 MB
 Length: 8:07 minutes
  
****************************************
 « Identifying and Monitoring Trends in Occupational Disease »
 Le suivi des profils et des tendances des maladies professionnelles dans différents secteurs d’activité peut aider à cibler les efforts de prévention. Nous discutons avec Paul Demers du Centre de recherche sur le cancer professionnel au sujet du Système de surveillance des maladies professionnelles (SSMP) et de ce que les données révèlent.
  
  
Date de diffusion : 14 juin 2022
 Taille du fichier : 5 MB
 Durée : 8 : 07 minutes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CCOHS Podcasts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How plant breeders’ rights are protected in Canada]]></title>
        <id>697fd7d7-f96e-4c85-ad69-dc3679269d1b</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-plant-breeders-rights-are-protected-in-canada-ltdEZjrz"/>
        <updated>2022-06-08T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Parker, Commissioner of the Plant Breeders' Rights Office within the Canadian Food Inspection Agency, explains the development of plant breeders' rights, how they are examined and how they function in Canada.
Explore online:
Plant Breeders' Rights... What are they?
Plant Breeders' Rights Office]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (The Canadian Intellectual Property Office, Anthony Parker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting a rope around antimicrobial resistance in cattle]]></title>
        <id>fe9d9457-d03b-4525-aaac-a587044ceca0</id>
        <link href="https://share.transistor.fm/s/a0151808"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When veterinarian Dr. Greg Dimmers noticed an alarming pattern of infection in beef cattle, he contacted microbiologist Dr. Tim McAllister to get some answers. Hear the two speak about their respective paths in the study of antimicrobial resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powered by Haloo: How artificial intelligence systems can be used to prepare trademark registration applications]]></title>
        <id>e2d845ad-2379-4ed7-9efa-87126177ff5e</id>
        <link href="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/powered-by-haloo-how-artificial-intelligence-systems-can-be-used-to-prepare-trademark-registration-applications-7z20x5UQ"/>
        <updated>2022-05-25T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julie MacDonell, Co-founder and CEO of Haloo discusses the importance of trademarks and how artificial intelligence is used at Haloo to partially replace manual searching in the trademark registration application process.
Explore online:
Learn more about trademarks and what the rules are concerning what can and cannot be registered at 
www.cipo.gc.ca/tm-guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CanadianIPVoices@ised-isde.gc.ca (The Canadian Intellectual Property Office)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>